affmore.com 2018-11-11

# LuckyDino – Simply Lucky. Casino! Play 7 Free Spins – LuckyDino

## Introduction

This Privacy Policy describes how Lucky Dino Gaming Limited, LLC and its affiliates ("Lucky Dino Gaming Limited ," "we," "our" or "us") collect, use, and share information in connection with your use of our websites (including [https://luckydino.com](https://luckydino.com/) and other websites operated by Lucky Dino Gaming Ltd, services, and applications (collectively, the "Services"). This Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") does not apply to information our customers may process when using our Services.  
Lucky Dino Gaming Limited is committed to protect the personal information you provide us with and we will take all reasonable precautions to ensure that all the data that you have submitted via the Website(s) remains safe. For this reason, we have created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you use our Services, why we collect this information and how we use the data collected.  
By submitting your information to Lucky Dino Gaming Limited and using our Website(s) you confirm your consent to our use of your personal data as set out in this document. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy and do not wish to provide us with the personal information we require, please do not use this Website.  
We may collect and receive information about users of our Services ("users," "you," or "your") from various sources, including: (i) information you provide through your user account on the Services (your "Account") if you register for the Services; (ii) your use of the Services; and (iii) from third-party websites, services, and partners.  
We recommend that you read this Privacy Policy in full to ensure you are fully informed. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or Lucky Dino Gaming Limited's data collection, use, and disclosure practices, please contact us at [privacy@luckydino.com](mailto:privacy@luckydino.com).

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

### Information You Provide

**Account Registration**  
When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, address, email address, and telephone number.

**Payment Information**  
When you add your financial account information to your Account, that information is directed to our third-party payment processor. This includes your use of credit card and on-line payment systems.

**User Content**  
Unless you have elected not to receive promotional information, we may also use your Personal Information, including your email address and phone number, to provide you with marketing communications regarding products, services and promotions that we think you may find interesting. Should you prefer to stop receiving marketing and other advertising material, you may opt out of this service by contacting our customer support service or sending us email on [support@luckydino.com](mailto:support@luckydino.com).

**Communications**  
If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, ip-address the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.  
The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.

**Information We Collect When You Use Our Services**  
 _Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies_  
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. In addition, when you use our Services, we may collect certain information automatically from your device. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, landing page, and referring URL. To collect this information, a cookie may be set on your computer or device when you visit our Services. Cookies contain a small amount of information that allows our web servers to recognise you. We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and/or clear gifs to record your preferences. We may also automatically collect information about your use of features of our Services, about the functionality of our Services, frequency of visits, and other information related to your interactions with the Services. We may track your use across different websites and services. In some countries, including countries in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), the information referenced above in this paragraph may be considered personal information under applicable data protection laws.

**Information We Receive from Third Parties**  
 _Third-Party Accounts_  
If you choose to link our Services to a third-party account, we will receive information about that account, such as your authentication token from the third-party account, to authorize linking. If you wish to limit the information available to us, you should visit the privacy settings of your third-party accounts to learn about your options.

**Third-Party Partners**  
We may also receive publicly available information about you from our third-party partners and combine it with data that we have about you.

## HOW WE USE INFORMATION

We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:

  * Provide, operate, and maintain our Services.
  * Providing you with customer support satisfaction and help you set up, operate and manage your account
  * Creating personal profiles for our customers, these may lead to Loyalty Points and Rewards.
  * Analysing customer trends through market study assessments.
  * Develop new products, services, features, and functionality.
  * Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the Service.
  * Processing your bets and transactions. This includes your use of credit card and on-line payment systems
  * Send you text messages, emails, postal mail and push notifications. Customers have a choice as to whether they would like to participate.
  * Providing our registered customers with information about our promotional offers.
  * Find and prevent fraud and money laundering and other irregular gaming activities.
  * For compliance purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service, or other legal rights, or as may be required by applicable laws and regulations or requested by any judicial process or governmental agency.

We may share information that you have given us to other companies within the Lucky Dino Gaming Limited and to our business partners. These companies will include our parent companies, their parent companies and all of the subsidiaries of these respective companies (the “Group”), as well as other companies with whom we carry out business. Data processing of your information may be undertaken by Lucky Dino Gaming Limited or by another company in the Group, which may use a third party to fulfil such data processing needs.  
You should also note that in order to provide you with an efficient service, we and/or our service providers might require transferring your personal data from one country to another in the European Union (EU) and European Free Trade Association (EFTA) regions and also to some data processors that may be based outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). Therefore, by browsing the Website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our (or our suppliers or sub-contractors) processing of your personal data in these countries. We shall always take all reasonable steps to ensure that your information and data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  
Personal data will always be safeguarded in accordance with legal requirements, for this reason it shall not be passed on to third parties, unless such disclosure is deemed suitable for your participation in our business and in the business carried out in collaboration with any of our business partners. This shall include the processing of your requests in relation to your use of our Brand/Products and/or the Games/Products or our business associates or unless the law expressly requires it. Relevant authorities, regulators, employees of Lucky Dino Gaming Limited, more specifically those forming part of Customer Support and the Payments and Fraud teams as well as other selected employees, shall also have access to your personal data for the purpose of executing their duties and providing you with assistance. You hereby consent to such disclosures.

We may share the information we collect in various ways, including the following:

_Aggregate Information_  
Where legally permissible, we may use and share information about users with our partners in aggregated or de-identified form that can’t reasonably be used to identify you.

_Vendors and Service Providers_  
We may share information with third-party vendors and service providers that provide services on our behalf, such as helping to provide our Services, for promotional and/or marketing purposes, and to provide you with information relevant to you such as product announcements, software updates, special offers, or other information.

_Information We Share When You Sign Up Through a Referral_  
If you sign up for our Services through a referral from a friend, we may share information with your referrer to let them know that you used their referral to sign up for our Services.

_Analytics_  
We use analytics providers such as Google Analytics. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect non-identifying information. Google provides some additional privacy options regarding its Analytics cookies at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.

_Business Transfers_  
Information may be disclosed and otherwise transferred to any potential acquirer, successor, or assignee as part of any proposed merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which information is transferred to one or more third parties as one of our business assets.

_As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures_  
We may also share information to (i) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request; (ii) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations hereof; (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; (iv) respond to your requests; or (v) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.

_With Your Consent_  
We may share information with your consent. But we never sell or otherwise transfer any personal information to third parties without a valid reason, namely reporting to legal authorities or law enforcement agencies.

_Affiliates and marketing partners_  
We're using affiliates and marketing partners who may advertise our services to you. We are not sharing any personal information with these partners and we do not take any responsibility for the services they are providing.

## LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.  
However, we will normally collect personal information from you only (i) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you; (ii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights; or (iii) where we have your consent to do so. We have a legitimate interest in operating our Services and communicating with you as necessary to provide these Services, for example when responding to your queries, improving our platform, undertaking marketing, or for the purposes of detecting or preventing illegal activities.  
In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you or may otherwise need the personal information to protect your vital interests or those of another person.  
If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information).

## THIRD-PARTY SERVICES

You may access other third-party services through the Services, for example by clicking on links to those third-party services from within the Services. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these third-party services, and we encourage you to carefully review their privacy policies.

## SECURITY

Lucky Dino Gaming Limited is committed to protecting your information. To do so, we employ a variety of security technologies and measures designed to protect information from unauthorised access, use, or disclosure. The measures we use are designed to provide a level of security appropriate to the risk of processing your personal information. However, please bear in mind that the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

## DATA RETENTION

We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, tax, or accounting requirements).  
When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymise it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

## ACCESS

If you are a registered user, you may access certain information associated with your Account by logging into our Services or emailing [support@luckydino.com](mailto:support@luckydino.com). If you terminate your Account, any public activity on your Account prior to deletion may remain stored on our servers.  
To protect your privacy and security, we may also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before updating or removing your information. The information you provide us may be archived or stored periodically by us according to backup processes conducted in the ordinary course of business for disaster recovery purposes. Your ability to access and correct your information may be temporarily limited where access and correction could: inhibit Lucky Dino Gaming Limited's ability to comply with a legal obligation; inhibit Lucky Dino Gaming Limited's ability to investigate, make or defend legal claims; result in disclosure of personal information about a third party; or result in breach of a contract or disclosure of trade secrets or other proprietary business information belonging to Lucky Dino Gaming Limited or a third party.

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the following data protection rights:  
If you wish to access, correct, update, or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by emailing [support@luckydino.com](mailto:support@luckydino.com).

In addition, you can object to the processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict the processing of your personal information, or request portability of your personal information. Again, you can exercise these rights by emailing [support@luckydino.com](mailto:support@luckydino.com).

You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the "unsubscribe" or "opt-out" link in the marketing emails we send you. To opt-out of other forms of marketing, please contact us by emailing [support@luckydino.com](mailto:support@luckydino.com) or chat on our website.

Similarly, if we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.  
We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

## YOUR CHOICES

You can use some of the features of the Services without registering, thereby limiting the type of information that we collect.  
You may unsubscribe from receiving certain promotional emails from us. If you wish to do so, simply follow the instructions found at the end of the email. Even if you unsubscribe, we may still contact you for informational, transactional, account-related, or similar purposes.  
Many browsers have an option for disabling cookies, which may prevent your browser from accepting new cookies or enable selective use of cookies. Please note that, if you choose not to accept cookies, some features and the personalisation of our Services may no longer work for you. You will continue to receive advertising material but it will not be tailored to your interests.

## CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Lucky Dino Gaming Limited does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 18, and children under 18 are prohibited from using our Services. If you learn that a child has provided us with personal information in violation of this Privacy Policy, you can alert us at [support@luckydino.com](mailto:support@luckydino.com).

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, so please review it frequently. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our websites. If we materially change the ways in which we use or share personal information previously collected from you through our Services, we will notify you through our Services, by email, or other communication.

## INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS

Lucky Dino Gaming Limited is a global business. We may transfer personal information to countries other than the country in which the data was originally collected. These countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at [privacy@luckydino.com](mailto:privacy@luckydino.com)

* * *
